

# Arjuna Panji Prakarsa

### Programmer

9

(+62) 81271310334



linkedin.com/in/arjunapanji



arjuna.panji97@gmail.com



https://github.com/arjunapanji21

I am a self taught programmer since 2013, starting my journey in web development using HTML, CSS and PHP native. In 2017, i attend the university and start learning application programming from structured to object-oriented programming with C# and Java. In the middle of 2018 i joined the robotic community in my university and deeply dive into robotic and automation system. Participated in Indonesian Robotic Contest in 2018 and 2019 and ended it with my thesis related to Machine Learning using Python and C/C++. After graduation i don't stop learning and keep improving my skills, try something new like game development using Unity Engine and Mobile Apps Development with Flutter. So many thing i want to do with programming, and i hope i can working for you or even working together with you and your team to develop something great for the future.

## **Experiences**

2020-07 - Present

2019-02 - 2019-08

2019-08 - 2020-07

2018-03 - 2019-02

# Full-stack Developer

GLT Production, Jambi, ID

- Specialized in Embedded Applications, IoT, Website, Game and Mobile Apps.

#### **Full-stack Developer**

PT. Ridikc Industries, Jambi, ID

- Specialized in Embedded Applications, IoT and Web Development.

#### **Senior Programmer and Team Leader**

Dinamika Bangsa University in Indonesian Robotic Contest 2019

- Develop an object detection for the robot using OpenCV Python.

### **Junior Programmer**

Dinamika Bangsa University in Indonesian Robotic Contest 2018

- Develop robot's logic for automation using C.

# 0

## **Educations**

2017 - 2021

BS in Computer Science University of Dinamika Bangsa Jambi, Indonesia.

- Graduated Magna Cum Laude with GPA 3.93/4
- Computer Laboratory Assistant
- Leader of Robotic Community

